<root>

	<styles>
		<include src="file://{resources}/styles/base_styles.css" />
		<include src="file://{resources}/styles/info_panels.css" />
	</styles>

	<script>
    (function()
    {
      CustomNetTables.SubscribeNetTableListener("game", UpdateCount);
      UpdateCount();
      ChangeFortune();
    })();
    function ResetFallout() 
    {
      GameEvents.SendCustomGameEventToServer( "reset_fallout", { } );
    }
    function UpdateCount()
    {
      $("#count").text = "\nHidden Fallout Men: " + CustomNetTables.GetTableValue("game", "count").value;
    }
    function ChangeFortune()
    {
      var wisdom = [
        "\nMy mind is a potato field ...",
        "\nWhat's the MATTER Sid? ... Is your BEVERAGE unsatisfactory?",
        "\nExcuse me, but didn't I tell you there's NO HOPE for the survival of\nOFFSET PRINTING?",
        "\nI'm having a MID-WEEK CRISIS!",
        "\nWhere's the Coke machine?  Tell me a joke!!",
        "\nI guess you guys got BIG MUSCLES from doing too much STUDYING!",
        "\nDid you move a lot of KOREAN STEAK KNIVES this trip, Dingy?",
        "\nI don't know WHY I said that ... I think it came from the FILLINGS in\nmy rear molars ...",
        "\nYOW!!  I'm in a very clever and adorable INSANE ASYLUM!!",
        "\nThe SAME WAVE keeps coming in and COLLAPSING like a rayon MUU-MUU ...",
        "\nNow KEN and BARBIE are PERMANENTLY ADDICTED to MIND-ALTERING DRUGS ...",
        "\nI haven't been married in over six years, but we had sexual counseling\nevery day from Oral Roberts!!",
        "\nCatsup and Mustard all over the place!  It's the Human Hamburger!",
        "\nWhat I need is a MATURE RELATIONSHIP with a FLOPPY DISK ...",
        "\nHello.  Just walk along and try NOT to think about your INTESTINES\nbeing almost FORTY YARDS LONG!!",
        "\nHELLO KITTY gang terrorizes town, family STICKERED to death!",
        "\nMake me look like LINDA RONSTADT again!!",
        "\nI want you to MEMORIZE the collected poems of EDNA ST VINCENT MILLAY\n... BACKWARDS!!",
        "\nI want to so HAPPY, the VEINS in my neck STAND OUT!!",
        "\nHELLO, everybody, I'm a HUMAN!!",
        "\nYou mean you don't want to watch WRESTLING from ATLANTA?",
        "\nI was making donuts and now I'm on a bus!",
        "\nThis MUST be a good party -- My RIB CAGE is being painfully pressed up\nagainst someone's MARTINI!!",
        "\nI selected E5 ... but I didn't hear \"Sam the Sham and the Pharoahs\"!",
        "\nI want a WESSON OIL lease!!",
        "\nAlright, you!!  Imitate a WOUNDED SEAL pleading for a PARKING SPACE!!",
        "\nMy vaseline is RUNNING...",
        "\nNow I understand the meaning of \"THE MOD SQUAD\"!",
        "\nMy face is new, my license is expired, and I'm under a doctor's care!!!!",
        "\nHey, wait a minute!!  I want a divorce!! ... you're not Clint Eastwood!!",
        "\nWell, here I am in AMERICA..  I LIKE it.  I HATE it.  I LIKE it.  I\nHATE it.  I LIKE it.  I HATE it.  I LIKE it.  I HATE it.  I LIKE ...\nEMOTIONS are SWEEPING over me!!",
        "\n... he dominates the DECADENT SUBWAY SCENE.",
        "\nI'm gliding over a NUCLEAR WASTE DUMP near ATLANTA, Georgia!!",
        "\nDIDI ... is that a MARTIAN name, or, are we in ISRAEL?",
        "\nDon't SANFORIZE me!!",
        "\nI request a weekend in Havana with Phil Silvers!",
        "\nI'm a GENIUS!  I want to dispute sentence structure with SUSAN SONTAG!!",
        "\nBut they went to MARS around 1953!!",
        "\nYow!  I just went below the poverty line!",
        "\nHere I am at the flea market but nobody is buying my urine sample bottles ...",
        "\nPEGGY FLEMMING is stealing BASKET BALLS to feed the babies in VERMONT.",
        "\nUH-OH!!  We're out of AUTOMOBILE PARTS and RUBBER GOODS!",
        "\nWhen I met th'POPE back in '58, I scrubbed him with a MILD SOAP or\nDETERGENT for 15 minutes.  He seemed to enjoy it ...",
        "\n... I have read the INSTRUCTIONS ...",
        "\nI am deeply CONCERNED and I want something GOOD for BREAKFAST!",
        "\nDo I have a lifestyle yet?",
        "\nI'm wet!  I'm wild!",
        "\nAn air of FRENCH FRIES permeates my nostrils!!",
        "\nLife is a POPULARITY CONTEST!  I'm REFRESHINGLY CANDID!!",
        "\nDoes someone from PEORIA have a SHORTER ATTENTION span than me?",
        "\nWhile you're chewing, think of STEVEN SPIELBERG'S bank account ...  his\nwill have the same effect as two \"STARCH BLOCKERS\"!",
        "\nThe appreciation of the average visual graphisticator alone is worth\nthe whole suaveness and decadence which abounds!!",
        "\nI'm encased in the lining of a pure pork sausage!!",
        "\nOn the road, ZIPPY is a pinhead without a purpose, but never without a POINT.",
        "\nKids, the seven basic food groups are GUM, PUFF PASTRY, PIZZA,\nPESTICIDES, ANTIBIOTICS, NUTRA-SWEET and MILK DUDS!!",
        "\nBoys, you have ALL been selected to LEAVE th' PLANET in 15 minutes!!",
        "\nHOORAY, Ronald!!  Now YOU can marry LINDA RONSTADT too!!",
        "\nNow I'm having INSIPID THOUGHTS about the beatiful, round wives of\nHOLLYWOOD MOVIE MOGULS encased in PLEXIGLASS CARS and being approached\nby SMALL BOYS selling FRUIT ...",
        "\nDidn't I buy a 1951 Packard from you last March in Cairo?",
        "\nNow my EMOTIONAL RESOURCES are heavily committed to 23% of the SMELTING\nand REFINING industry of the state of NEVADA!!",
        "\nI always have fun because I'm out of my mind!!!",
        "\nAll of life is a blur of Republicans and meat!",
        "\nIn Newark the laundromats are open 24 hours a day!",
        "\nEither CONFESS now or we go to \"PEOPLE'S COURT\"!!",
        "\nI hope I bought the right relish ... zzzzzzzzz ...",
        "\nActually, what I'd like is a little toy spaceship!!",
        "\n... the MYSTERIANS are in here with my CORDUROY SOAP DISH!!",
        "\nI want to read my new poem about pork brains and outer space ...",
        "\nHello?  Enema Bondage?  I'm calling because I want to be happy, I guess ...",
        "\nover in west Philadelphia a puppy is vomiting ...",
        "\nI'm changing the CHANNEL ... But all I get is commercials for \"RONCO\nMIRACLE BAMBOO STEAMERS\"!",
        "\nIf Robert Di Niro assassinates Walter Slezak, will Jodie Foster marry Bonzo??",
        "\nHmmm ... a PINHEAD, during an EARTHQUAKE, encounters an ALL-MIDGET\nFIDDLE ORCHESTRA ... ha ... ha ...",
        "\nI didn't order any WOO-WOO ... Maybe a YUBBA ... But no WOO-WOO!",
        "\nI'm totally DESPONDENT over the LIBYAN situation and the price of CHICKEN ...",
        "\nI feel better about world problems now!",
        "\nI need to discuss BUY-BACK PROVISIONS with at least six studio SLEAZEBALLS!!",
        "\nI just had my entire INTESTINAL TRACT coated with TEFLON!",
        "\nYow!  Am I having fun yet?",
        "\nWait ... is this a FUN THING or the END of LIFE in Petticoat Junction??",
        "\nOkay ... I'm going home to write the \"I HATE RUBIK's CUBE HANDBOOK FOR\nDEAD CAT LOVERS\" ...",
        "\nDo you have exactly what I want in a plaid poindexter bar bat??",
        "\nDo you like \"TENDER VITTLES\"?",
        "\nLaundry is the fifth dimension!!  ... um ... um ... th' washing machine\nis a black hole and the pink socks are bus drivers who just fell in!!",
        "\nEisenhower!!  Your mimeograph machine upsets my stomach!!",
        "\nI guess it was all a DREAM ... or an episode of HAWAII FIVE-O ...",
        "\nBut was he mature enough last night at the lesbian masquerade?",
        "\nNEWARK has been REZONED!!  DES MOINES has been REZONED!!",
        "\nWill it improve my CASH FLOW?",
        "\nhubub, hubub, HUBUB, hubub, hubub, hubub, HUBUB, hubub, hubub, hubub.",
        "\nMy polyvinyl cowboy wallet was made in Hong Kong by Montgomery Clift!",
        "\nAre we THERE yet?",
        "\nDo you guys know we just passed thru a BLACK HOLE in space?",
        "\nDid I SELL OUT yet??",
        "\nLook!  A ladder!  Maybe it leads to heaven, or a sandwich!",
        "\nHmmm ... an arrogant bouquet with a subtle suggestion of POLYVINYL\nCHLORIDE ...",
        "\nI'm having BEAUTIFUL THOUGHTS about the INSIPID WIVES of smug and\nwealthy CORPORATE LAWYERS ...",
        "\nMy Aunt MAUREEN was a military advisor to IKE & TINA TURNER!!",
        "\nI'm having a BIG BANG THEORY!!",
        "\nI feel ... JUGULAR ...",
        "\nOVER the underpass!  UNDER the overpass!  Around the FUTURE and BEYOND REPAIR!!",
        "\nI'm continually AMAZED at th'breathtaking effects of WIND EROSION!!",
        "\n\tTalking Pinhead Blues:\nOh, I LOST my ``HELLO KITTY'' DOLL and I get BAD reception on channel\n    TWENTY-SIX!!\n\nTh'HOSTESS FACTORY is closin' down and I just heard ZASU PITTS has been\n    DEAD for YEARS..  (sniff)\n\nMy PLATFORM SHOE collection was CHEWED up by th' dog, ALEXANDER HAIG\n    won't let me take a SHOWER 'til Easter ... (snurf)\n\nSo I went to the kitchen, but WALNUT PANELING whup me upside mah HAID!!\n    (on no, no, no..  Heh, heh)",
        "\nHey, waiter!  I want a NEW SHIRT and a PONY TAIL with lemon sauce!",
        "\n-- I love KATRINKA because she drives a PONTIAC.  We're going away\nnow.  I fed the cat.",
        "\nI'm RELIGIOUS!!  I love a man with a HAIRPIECE!!  Equip me with MISSILES!!",
        "\nTh' MIND is the Pizza Palace of th' SOUL",
        "\nThis PORCUPINE knows his ZIPCODE ... And he has \"VISA\"!!",
        "\nYou were s'posed to laugh!",
        "\nHow many retured bricklayers from FLORIDA are out purchasing PENCIL\nSHARPENERS right NOW??",
        "\nBarbie says, Take quaaludes in gin and go to a disco right away!\nBut Ken says, WOO-WOO!!  No credit at \"Mr. Liquor\"!!",
        "\nI own seven-eighths of all the artists in downtown Burbank!",
        "\nIf I had a Q-TIP, I could prevent th' collapse of NEGOTIATIONS!!",
        "\nYes, but will I see the EASTER BUNNY in skintight leather at an IRON\nMAIDEN concert?",
        "\nAre we THERE yet?  My MIND is a SUBMARINE!!",
        "\nSomewhere in Tenafly, New Jersey, a chiropractor is viewing \"Leave it\nto Beaver\"!",
        "\nGibble, Gobble, we ACCEPT YOU ...",
        "\nDo you think the \"Monkees\" should get gas on odd or even days?",
        "\nMy EARS are GONE!!",
        "\nGee, I feel kind of LIGHT in the head now, knowing I can't make my\nsatellite dish PAYMENTS!",
        "\nI know th'MAMBO!!  I have a TWO-TONE CHEMISTRY SET!!",
        "\nWhy don't you ever enter any CONTESTS, Marvin??  Don't you know your\nown ZIPCODE?",
        "\nIf I am elected, the concrete barriers around the WHITE HOUSE will be\nreplaced by tasteful foam replicas of ANN MARGARET!",
        "\nA shapely CATHOLIC SCHOOLGIRL is FIDGETING inside my costume..",
        "\nPUNK ROCK!!  DISCO DUCK!!  BIRTH CONTROL!!",
        "\nIsn't this my STOP?!",
        "\nBARBARA STANWYCK makes me nervous!!",
        "\nAmerica!!  I saw it all!!  Vomiting!  Waving!  JERRY FALWELLING into\nyour void tube of UHF oblivion!!  SAFEWAY of the mind ...",
        "\nLet me do my TRIBUTE to FISHNET STOCKINGS ...",
        "\nONE LIFE TO LIVE for ALL MY CHILDREN in ANOTHER WORLD all THE DAYS OF OUR LIVES.",
        "\nUh-oh!!  I'm having TOO MUCH FUN!!",
        "\nYow!  Am I in Milwaukee?",
        "\nThe entire CHINESE WOMEN'S VOLLEYBALL TEAM all share ONE personality --\nand have since BIRTH!!",
        "\nJesuit priests are DATING CAREER DIPLOMATS!!",
        "\nNow that I have my \"APPLE\", I comprehend COST ACCOUNTING!!",
        "\nLike I always say -- nothing can beat the BRATWURST here in DUSSELDORF!!",
        "\nThis is a NO-FRILLS flight -- hold th' CANADIAN BACON!!",
        "\nIt don't mean a THING if you ain't got that SWING!!",
        "\nI brought my BOWLING BALL -- and some DRUGS!!",
        "\nONE:    I will donate my entire \"BABY HUEY\" comic book collection to\n\tthe downtown PLASMA CENTER ...\nTWO:\tI won't START a BAND called \"KHADAFY & THE HIT SQUAD\" ...\nTHREE:\tI won't ever TUMBLE DRY my FOX TERRIER again!!",
        "A can of ASPARAGUS, 73 pigeons, some LIVE ammo, and a FROZEN DAQUIRI!!",
        "\nI know things about TROY DONAHUE that can't even be PRINTED!!",
        "\nPlease come home with me ... I have Tylenol!!",
        "\nIt's OKAY -- I'm an INTELLECTUAL, too.",
        "\nI want another RE-WRITE on my CEASAR SALAD!!",
        "\nNATHAN ... your PARENTS were in a CARCRASH!!  They're VOIDED -- They\nCOLLAPSED They had no CHAINSAWS ... They had no MONEY MACHINES ... They\ndid PILLS in SKIMPY GRASS SKIRTS ... Nathan, I EMULATED them ... but\nthey were OFF-KEY ...",
        "\nIs this TERMINAL fun?",
        "\nI'm DESPONDENT ... I hope there's something DEEP-FRIED under this\nminiature DOMED STADIUM ...",
        "\nI'm receiving a coded message from EUBIE BLAKE!!",
        "\nNow I'm being INVOLUNTARILY shuffled closer to the CLAM DIP with the\nBROKEN PLASTIC FORKS in it!!",
        "\nWhen you get your PH.D. will you get able to work at BURGER KING?",
        "\n... ich bin in einem dusenjet ins jahr 53 vor chr ... ich lande im\nantiken Rom ...  einige gladiatoren spielen scrabble ... ich rieche\nPIZZA ...",
        "\nPsychoanalysis??  I thought this was a nude rap session!!!",
        "\nA wide-eyed, innocent UNICORN, poised delicately in a MEADOW filled\nwith LILACS, LOLLIPOPS & small CHILDREN at the HUSH of twilight??",
        "\nIt's NO USE ... I've gone to \"CLUB MED\"!!",
        "\nYow!  Are we laid back yet?",
        "\nYow!  We're going to a new disco!",
        "\nOn SECOND thought, maybe I'll heat up some BAKED BEANS and watch REGIS\nPHILBIN ...  It's GREAT to be ALIVE!!",
        "\nBoy, am I glad it's only 1971...",
        "\nWe just joined the civil hair patrol!",
        "\nI think my career is ruined!",
        "\nThe Korean War must have been fun.",
        "\nI wish I was a sex-starved manicurist found dead in the Bronx!!",
        "\nSometime in 1993 NANCY SINATRA will lead a BLOODLESS COUP on GUAM!!",
        "\nI joined scientology at a garage sale!!",
        "\nNANCY!!  Why is everything RED?!",
        "\nI'm not an Iranian!!  I voted for Dianne Feinstein!!",
        "\nDid I do an INCORRECT THING??",
        "\n... this must be what it's like to be a COLLEGE GRADUATE!!",
        "\nSend your questions to ``ASK ZIPPY'', Box 40474, San Francisco, CA\n94140, USA",
        "\nI had pancake makeup for brunch!",
        "\n-- I have seen the FUN --",
        "\nLeona, I want to CONFESS things to you ... I want to WRAP you in a SCARLET\nROBE trimmed with POLYVINYL CHLORIDE ... I want to EMPTY your ASHTRAYS ...",
        "\nYou should all JUMP UP AND DOWN for TWO HOURS while I decide on a NEW CAREER!!",
        "\nDon't hit me!!  I'm in the Twilight Zone!!!",
        "\nIs it 1974?  What's for SUPPER?  Can I spend my COLLEGE FUND in one\nwild afternoon??",
        "\nI wish I was on a Cincinnati street corner holding a clean dog!",
        "\nHere we are in America ... when do we collect unemployment?",
        "\nLet's all show human CONCERN for REVERAND MOON's legal difficulties!!",
        "\nNipples, dimples, knuckles, NICKLES, wrinkles, pimples!!",
        "\nToday, THREE WINOS from DETROIT sold me a framed photo of TAB HUNTER\nbefore his MAKEOVER!",
        "\nHold the MAYO & pass the COSMIC AWARENESS ...",
        "\n\"This is a job for BOB VIOLENCE and SCUM, the INCREDIBLY STUPID MUTANT DOG.\"\n\t\t-- Bob Violence",
        "\nWhere do your SOCKS go when you lose them in th' WASHER?",
        "\nI feel partially hydrogenated!",
        "\nI'm a nuclear submarine under the polar ice cap and I need a Kleenex!",
        "\nMr and Mrs PED, can I borrow 26.7% of the RAYON TEXTILE production of\nthe INDONESIAN archipelago?",
        "\nAre we on STRIKE yet?",
        "\nI want you to organize my PASTRY trays ... my TEA-TINS are gleaming in\nformation like a ROW of DRUM MAJORETTES -- please don't be FURIOUS with me --",
        "\nIs this the line for the latest whimsical YUGOSLAVIAN drama which also\nmakes you want to CRY and reconsider the VIETNAM WAR?",
        "\nANN JILLIAN'S HAIR makes LONI ANDERSON'S HAIR look like RICARDO\nMONTALBAN'S HAIR!",
        "\nHow do you explain Wayne Newton's POWER over millions?  It's th' MOUSTACHE\n...  Have you ever noticed th' way it radiates SINCERITY, HONESTY & WARMTH?\nIt's a MOUSTACHE you want to take HOME and introduce to NANCY SINATRA!",
        "\nI invented skydiving in 1989!",
        "\nI'm in direct contact with many advanced fun CONCEPTS.",
        "\nYOW!!  Everybody out of the GENETIC POOL!",
        "\nIf I pull this SWITCH I'll be RITA HAYWORTH!!  Or a SCIENTOLOGIST!",
        "\nMERYL STREEP is my obstetrician!",
        "\nWell, O.K.  I'll compromise with my principles because of EXISTENTIAL DESPAIR!",
        "\nHow's it going in those MODULAR LOVE UNITS??",
        "\nI feel like I am sharing a ``CORN-DOG'' with NIKITA KHRUSCHEV ...",
        "\nYow!  Did something bad happen or am I in a drive-in movie??",
        "\nLook DEEP into the OPENINGS!!  Do you see any ELVES or EDSELS ... or a\nHIGHBALL?? ...",
        "\nI'll eat ANYTHING that's BRIGHT BLUE!!",
        "\nHe probably just wants to take over my CELLS and then EXPLODE inside me\nlike a BARREL of runny CHOPPED LIVER!  Or maybe he'd like to\nPSYCHOLIGICALLY TERRORISE ME until I have no objection to a RIGHT-WING\nMILITARY TAKEOVER of my apartment!!  I guess I should call AL PACINO!",
        "\nAnd furthermore, my bowling average is unimpeachable!!!",
        "\nYOU!!  Give me the CUTEST, PINKEST, most charming little VICTORIAN\nDOLLHOUSE you can find!!  An make it SNAPPY!!",
        "\nThank god!! ... It's HENNY YOUNGMAN!!",
        "\nThere's a little picture of ED MCMAHON doing BAD THINGS to JOAN RIVERS\nin a $200,000 MALIBU BEACH HOUSE!!",
        "\nI'm rated PG-34!!",
        "\nHUMAN REPLICAS are inserted into VATS of NUTRITIONAL YEAST ...",
        "\nSANTA CLAUS comes down a FIRE ESCAPE wearing bright blue LEG WARMERS\n... He scrubs the POPE with a mild soap or detergent for 15 minutes,\nstarring JANE FONDA!!",
        "\n... If I had heart failure right now, I couldn't be a more fortunate man!!",
        "\nI am NOT a nut....",
        "\nPeople humiliating a salami!",
        "\nI would like to urinate in an OVULAR, porcelain pool --",
        "\nToes, knees, NIPPLES.  Toes, knees, nipples, KNUCKLES ...\nNipples, dimples, knuckles, NICKLES, wrinkles, pimples!!",
        "\nSpreading peanut butter reminds me of opera!!  I wonder why?",
        "\nWhat PROGRAM are they watching?",
        "\nI'm dressing up in an ill-fitting IVY-LEAGUE SUIT!!  Too late...",
        "\nHere I am in the POSTERIOR OLFACTORY LOBULE but I don't see CARL SAGAN\nanywhere!!",
        "\nAre we live or on tape?",
        "\nJesus is my POSTMASTER GENERAL ...",
        "\nDid an Italian CRANE OPERATOR just experience uninhibited sensations in\na MALIBU HOT TUB?",
        "\nIf a person is FAMOUS in this country, they have to go on the ROAD for\nMONTHS at a time and have their name misspelled on the SIDE of a\nGREYHOUND SCENICRUISER!!",
        "\nYOW!!  Now I understand advanced MICROBIOLOGY and th' new TAX REFORM laws!!",
        "\nI love ROCK 'N ROLL!  I memorized the all WORDS to \"WIPE-OUT\" in\n1965!!",
        "\nWorld War III?  No thanks!",
        "\nSomewhere in suburban Honolulu, an unemployed bellhop is whipping up a\nbatch of illegal psilocybin chop suey!!",
        "\nMy mind is making ashtrays in Dayton ...",
        "\nLBJ, LBJ, how many JOKES did you tell today??!",
        "\nHand me a pair of leather pants and a CASIO keyboard -- I'm living for today!",
        "\nI had a lease on an OEDIPUS COMPLEX back in '81 ...",
        "\nI know how to do SPECIAL EFFECTS!!",
        "\nMy uncle Murray conquered Egypt in 53 B.C.  And I can prove it too!!",
        "\nI like the way ONLY their mouths move ...  They look like DYING OYSTERS",
        "\nYOW!!  Up ahead!  It's a DONUT HUT!!",
        "\nMy LESLIE GORE record is BROKEN ...",
        "\nI don't believe there really IS a GAS SHORTAGE.. I think it's all just\na BIG HOAX on the part of the plastic sign salesmen -- to sell more numbers!!",
        "\nEverybody gets free BORSCHT!",
        "\nNow, let's SEND OUT for QUICHE!!",
        "\nOKAY!!  Turn on the sound ONLY for TRYNEL CARPETING, FULLY-EQUIPPED\nR.V.'S and FLOATATION SYSTEMS!!",
        "\nI was born in a Hostess Cupcake factory before the sexual revolution!",
        "\nNow I'm concentrating on a specific tank battle toward the end of World War II!",
        "\nWill this never-ending series of PLEASURABLE EVENTS never cease?",
        "\nRELATIVES!!",
        "\n... or were you driving the PONTIAC that HONKED at me in MIAMI last Tuesday?",
        "\nWHO sees a BEACH BUNNY sobbing on a SHAG RUG?!",
        "\nConcentrate on th'cute, li'l CARTOON GUYS!  Remember the SERIAL\nNUMBERS!!  Follow the WHIPPLE AVE. EXIT!!  Have a FREE PEPSI!!  Turn\nLEFT at th'HOLIDAY INN!!  JOIN the CREDIT WORLD!!  MAKE me an OFFER!!!",
        "\nHe is the MELBA-BEING ... the ANGEL CAKE ... XEROX him ... XEROX him --",
        "\nIt's a lot of fun being alive ... I wonder if my bed is made?!?",
        "\nWhen this load is DONE I think I'll wash it AGAIN ...",
        "\nNot SENSUOUS ... only \"FROLICSOME\" ... and in need of DENTAL WORK ... in PAIN!!!",
        "\nGo on, EMOTE!  I was RAISED on thought balloons!!",
        "\nI'm having an emotional outburst!!",
        "\nWhere does it go when you flush?",
        "\nHello...  IRON CURTAIN?  Send over a SAUSAGE PIZZA!  World War III?  No thanks!",
        "\nI'm young ... I'm HEALTHY ... I can HIKE THRU CAPT GROGAN'S LUMBAR REGIONS!",
        "\nHalf a mind is a terrible thing to waste!",
        "\nWhere's SANDY DUNCAN?",
        "\nI appoint you ambassador to Fantasy Island!!!",
        "\nAll this time I've been VIEWING a RUSSIAN MIDGET SODOMIZE a HOUSECAT!",
        "\nHmmm ... a CRIPPLED ACCOUNTANT with a FALAFEL sandwich is HIT by a\nTROLLEY-CAR ...",
        "\nYow!  Is my fallout shelter termite proof?",
        "\nYow!  I threw up on my window!",
        "\nAn INK-LING?  Sure -- TAKE one!!  Did you BUY any COMMUNIST UNIFORMS??",
        "\nI HAVE to buy a new \"DODGE MISER\" and two dozen JORDACHE JEANS because\nmy viewscreen is \"USER-FRIENDLY\"!!",
        "\nYow!  Now we can become alcoholics!",
        "\nHas everybody got HALVAH spread all over their ANKLES?? ...  Now, it's\ntime to \"HAVE A NAGEELA\"!!",
        "\nGOOD-NIGHT, everybody ... Now I have to go administer FIRST-AID to my\npet LEISURE SUIT!!",
        "\nNow I am depressed ...",
        "\nYow!  And then we could sit on the hoods of cars at stop lights!",
        "\nUH-OH!!  I put on \"GREAT HEAD-ON TRAIN COLLISIONS of the 50's\" by\nmistake!!!",
        "\nI KAISER ROLL?!  What good is a Kaiser Roll without a little COLE SLAW\non the SIDE?",
        "\nGive them RADAR-GUIDED SKEE-BALL LANES and VELVEETA BURRITOS!!",
        "\nI have a very good DENTAL PLAN.  Thank you.",
        "\nMy BIOLOGICAL ALARM CLOCK just went off ... It has noiseless DOZE\nFUNCTION and full kitchen!!",
        "\nI'm also against BODY-SURFING!!",
        "\nAm I in GRADUATE SCHOOL yet?",
        "\nWHOA!!  Ken and Barbie are having TOO MUCH FUN!!  It must be the\nNEGATIVE IONS!!",
        "\nI'm pretending I'm pulling in a TROUT!  Am I doing it correctly??",
        "\nWhy are these athletic shoe salesmen following me??",
        "\nOMNIVERSAL AWARENESS??  Oh, YEH!!  First you need four GALLONS of JELL-O\nand a BIG WRENCH!! ... I think you drop th'WRENCH in the JELL-O as if\nit was a FLAVOR, or an INGREDIENT ... ... or ... I ... um ... WHERE'S\nthe WASHING MACHINES?",
        "\nAll of a sudden, I want to THROW OVER my promising ACTING CAREER, grow\na LONG BLACK BEARD and wear a BASEBALL HAT!! ...  Although I don't know WHY!!",
        "\nYour CHEEKS sit like twin NECTARINES above a MOUTH that knows no BOUNDS --",
        "\nI just heard the SEVENTIES were over!!  And I was just getting in touch\nwith my LEISURE SUIT!!",
        "\nI want to dress you up as TALLULAH BANKHEAD and cover you with VASELINE\nand WHEAT THINS ...",
        "\nSomewhere in DOWNTOWN BURBANK a prostitute is OVERCOOKING a LAMB CHOP!!",
        "\nDON'T go!!  I'm not HOWARD COSELL!!  I know POLISH JOKES ... WAIT!!\nDon't go!!  I AM Howard Cosell! ... And I DON'T know Polish jokes!!",
        "\nI am having FUN...  I wonder if it's NET FUN or GROSS FUN?",
        "\nIs something VIOLENT going to happen to a GARBAGE CAN?",
        "\nAs President I have to go vacuum my coin collection!",
        "\nMY income is ALL disposable!",
        "\nHiccuping & trembling into the WASTE DUMPS of New Jersey like some\ndrunken CABBAGE PATCH DOLL, coughing in line at FIORUCCI'S!!",
        "\n... the HIGHWAY is made out of LIME JELLO and my HONDA is a barbequeued\nOYSTER!  Yum!",
        "\n... I don't know why but, suddenly, I want to discuss declining I.Q.\nLEVELS with a blue ribbon SENATE SUB-COMMITTEE!",
        "\nMy pants just went to high school in the Carlsbad Caverns!!!",
        "\nWorld War Three can be averted by adherence to a strictly enforced dress code!",
        "\nJAPAN is a WONDERFUL planet -- I wonder if we'll ever reach their level\nof COMPARATIVE SHOPPING ...",
        "\nYow!  It's a hole all the way to downtown Burbank!",
        "\nMy NOSE is NUMB!",
        "\nQuick, sing me the BUDAPEST NATIONAL ANTHEM!!",
        "\nSo, if we convert SUPPLY-SIDE SOYABEAN FUTURES into HIGH-YIELD T-BILL\nINDICATORS, the PRE-INFLATIONARY risks will DWINDLE to a rate of 2\nSHOPPING SPREES per EGGPLANT!!",
        "\nIf elected, Zippy pledges to each and every American a 55-year-old houseboy ...",
        "\nYow!  I'm having a quadrophonic sensation of two winos alone in a steel mill!",
        "\nYOU PICKED KARL MALDEN'S NOSE!!",
        "\nI wonder if I should put myself in ESCROW!!",
        "\n",
        "\nHAIR TONICS, please!!",
        "\nYow!  I'm imagining a surfer van filled with soy sauce!",
        "\nWell, I'm a classic ANAL RETENTIVE!!  And I'm looking for a way to\nVICARIOUSLY experience some reason to LIVE!!",
        "\nThese PRESERVES should be FORCE-FED to PENTAGON OFFICIALS!!",
        "\nFROZEN ENTREES may be flung by members of opposing SWANSON SECTS ...",
        "\nIs this an out-take from the \"BRADY BUNCH\"?",
        "\nI have seen these EGG EXTENDERS in my Supermarket ... I have read the\nINSTRUCTIONS ...",
        "\nMary Tyler Moore's SEVENTH HUSBAND is wearing my DACRON TANK TOP in a\ncheap hotel in HONOLULU!",
        "\n... I see TOILET SEATS ...",
        "\nThe Osmonds!  You are all Osmonds!!  Throwing up on a freeway at dawn!!!",
        "\nOne FISHWICH coming up!!",
        "\nMy nose feels like a bad Ronald Reagan movie ...",
        "\nI can't decide which WRONG TURN to make first!!  I wonder if BOB\nGUCCIONE has these problems!",
        "\nI want to kill everyone here with a cute colorful Hydrogen Bomb!!",
        "\nSomeone in DAYTON, Ohio is selling USED CARPETS to a SERBO-CROATIAN",
        "\nI represent a sardine!!",
        "\nClear the laundromat!!  This whirl-o-matic just had a nuclear meltdown!!",
        "\nI'd like MY data-base JULIENNED and stir-fried!",
        "\nI wonder if there's anything GOOD on tonight?",
        "\nWow!  Look!!  A stray meatball!!  Let's interview it!",
        "\nI just remembered something about a TOAD!",
        "\nI'm pretending that we're all watching PHIL SILVERS instead of RICARDO\nMONTALBAN!",
        "\nI'm GLAD I remembered to XEROX all my UNDERSHIRTS!!",
        "\nAre you selling NYLON OIL WELLS??  If so, we can use TWO DOZEN!!",
        "\nWe are now enjoying total mutual interaction in an imaginary hot tub ...",
        "\nYow!  Are you the self-frying president?",
        "\nTONY RANDALL!  Is YOUR life a PATIO of FUN??",
        "\nTAILFINS!! ... click ...",
        "\nINSIDE, I have the same personality disorder as LUCY RICARDO!!",
        "\nVote for ME -- I'm well-tapered, half-cocked, ill-conceived and TAX-DEFERRED!",
        "\nLOOK!!  Sullen American teens wearing MADRAS shorts and \"Flock of\nSeagulls\" HAIRCUTS!",
        "\nAll I can think of is a platter of organic PRUNE CRISPS being trampled\nby an army of swarthy, Italian LOUNGE SINGERS ...",
        "\nI've got an IDEA!!  Why don't I STARE at you so HARD, you forget your\nSOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER!!",
        "\nI want the presidency so bad I can already taste the hors d'oeuvres.",
        "\nTex SEX!  The HOME of WHEELS!  The dripping of COFFEE!!  Take me to\nMinnesota but don't EMBARRASS me!!",
        "\nWith YOU, I can be MYSELF ...  We don't NEED Dan Rather ...",
        "\n... I'm IMAGINING a sensuous GIRAFFE, CAVORTING in the BACK ROOM\nof a KOSHER DELI --",
        "\nThere is no TRUTH.  There is no REALITY.  There is no CONSISTENCY.\nThere are no ABSOLUTE STATEMENTS.   I'm very probably wrong.",
        "\nI just got my PRINCE bumper sticker ... But now I can't remember WHO he is ...",
        "\nThey collapsed ... like nuns in the street ... they had no teen\nappeal!",
        "\n... I don't like FRANK SINATRA or his CHILDREN.",
        "\nI'm definitely not in Omaha!",
        "\nMMM-MM!!  So THIS is BIO-NEBULATION! ",
        "\nHello.  I know the divorce rate among unmarried Catholic Alaskan females!!",
        "\nDid YOU find a DIGITAL WATCH in YOUR box of VELVEETA?",
        "\nHmmm ... A hash-singer and a cross-eyed guy were SLEEPING on a deserted\nisland, when ...",
        "\nI'm a fuschia bowling ball somewhere in Brittany",
        "\nSHHHH!!  I hear SIX TATTOOED TRUCK-DRIVERS tossing ENGINE BLOCKS into\nempty OIL DRUMS ...",
        "\nBI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-BI-",
        "\nYou mean now I can SHOOT YOU in the back and further BLUR th'\ndistinction between FANTASY and REALITY?",
        "\n... I think I'd better go back to my DESK and toy with a few common\nMISAPPREHENSIONS ...",
        "\nI can't think about that.  It doesn't go with HEDGES in the shape of\nLITTLE LULU -- or ROBOTS making BRICKS ...",
        "\nI have a VISION!  It's a RANCID double-FISHWICH on an ENRICHED BUN!!",
        "\nI have a TINY BOWL in my HEAD",
        "\nPlace me on a BUFFER counter while you BELITTLE several BELLHOPS in the\nTrianon Room!!  Let me one of your SUBSIDIARIES!",
        "\nI feel like I'm in a Toilet Bowl with a thumbtack in my forehead!!",
        "\ndoes your DRESSING ROOM have enough ASPARAGUS?",
        "\n... I want FORTY-TWO TRYNEL FLOATATION SYSTEMS installed within\nSIX AND A HALF HOURS!!!",
        "\nThe PINK SOCKS were ORIGINALLY from 1952!!  But they went to MARS\naround 1953!!",
        "\nYow!  Are we wet yet?",
        "\nI'm sitting on my SPEED QUEEN ... To me, it's ENJOYABLE ... I'm WARM\n... I'm VIBRATORY ...",
        "\nI want EARS!  I want two ROUND BLACK EARS to make me feel warm 'n secure!!",
        "\nI fill MY industrial waste containers with old copies of the \"WATCHTOWER\"\nand then add HAWAIIAN PUNCH to the top ...  They look NICE in the yard ...",
        "\nAre the STEWED PRUNES still in the HAIR DRYER?",
        "\nI'm shaving!!  I'M SHAVING!!",
        "\nI'm mentally OVERDRAWN!  What's that SIGNPOST up ahead?  Where's ROD\nSTERLING when you really need him?",
        "\nAre you mentally here at Pizza Hut??",
        "\nYou can't hurt me!!  I have an ASSUMABLE MORTGAGE!!",
        "\nLook into my eyes and try to forget that you have a Macy's charge card!",
        "\nYow!  Maybe I should have asked for my Neutron Bomb in PAISLEY --",
        "\nThis ASEXUAL PIG really BOILS my BLOOD ... He's so ... so ... URGENT!!",
        "\nWhy is everything made of Lycra Spandex?",
        "\nYouth of today!  Join me in a mass rally for traditional mental\nattitudes!",
        "\nI demand IMPUNITY!",
        "\nWhen you said \"HEAVILY FORESTED\" it reminded me of an overdue CLEANING\nBILL ... Don't you SEE?  O'Grogan SWALLOWED a VALUABLE COIN COLLECTION\nand HAD to murder the ONLY MAN who KNEW!!",
        "\nFirst, I'm going to give you all the ANSWERS to today's test ...  So\njust plug in your SONY WALKMANS and relax!!",
        "\nI used to be a FUNDAMENTALIST, but then I heard about the HIGH\nRADIATION LEVELS and bought an ENCYCLOPEDIA!!",
        "\nI hope the ``Eurythmics'' practice birth control ...",
        "\nI think I'll KILL myself by leaping out of this 14th STORY WINDOW while\nreading ERICA JONG'S poetry!!",
        "\nI Know A Joke!!",
        "\nThousands of days of civilians ... have produced a ... feeling for the\naesthetic modules --",
        "\nAm I accompanied by a PARENT or GUARDIAN?",
        "\nThe fact that 47 PEOPLE are yelling and sweat is cascading down my\nSPINAL COLUMN is fairly enjoyable!!",
        "\nI smell a RANCID CORN DOG!",
        "\nAre you still an ALCOHOLIC?",
        "\nEverybody is going somewhere!!  It's probably a garage sale or a\ndisaster Movie!!",
        "\nWas my SOY LOAF left out in th'RAIN?  It tastes REAL GOOD!!",
        "\nI'm QUIETLY reading the latest issue of \"BOWLING WORLD\" while my wife\nand two children stand QUIETLY BY ...",
        "\nI wonder if I could ever get started in the credit world?",
        "\nHow do I get HOME?",
        "\nWell, I'm INVISIBLE AGAIN ... I might as well pay a visit to the LADIES \nROOM ...",
        "\nRemember, in 2039, MOUSSE & PASTA will be available ONLY by prescription!!",
        "\nThis TOPS OFF my partygoing experience!  Someone I DON'T LIKE is\ntalking to me about a HEART-WARMING European film ...",
        "\nUH-OH!!  I think KEN is OVER-DUE on his R.V. PAYMENTS and HE'S having a\nNERVOUS BREAKDOWN too!!  Ha ha.",
        "\nIs this going to involve RAW human ecstasy?",
        "\nAm I SHOPLIFTING?",
        "\nFEELINGS are cascading over me!!!",
        "\nI'm thinking about DIGITAL READ-OUT systems and computer-generated\nIMAGE FORMATIONS ...",
        "\nI'll show you MY telex number if you show me YOURS ...",
        "\nMy haircut is totally traditional!",
        "\nI'm having an EMOTIONAL OUTBURST!!  But, uh, WHY is there a WAFFLE in\nmy PAJAMA POCKET??",
        "\nLet's send the Russians defective lifestyle accessories!",
        "\nContent:  80% POLYESTER, 20% DACRONi ... The waitress's UNIFORM sheds\nTARTAR SAUCE like an 8\" by 10\" GLOSSY ...",
        "\nShould I get locked in the PRINCICAL'S OFFICE today -- or have a VASECTOMY??",
        "\nNow I think I just reached the state of HYPERTENSION that comes JUST\nBEFORE you see the TOTAL at the SAFEWAY CHECKOUT COUNTER!",
        "\nIt was a JOKE!!  Get it??  I was receiving messages from DAVID LETTERMAN!!\nYOW!!",
        "\nI put aside my copy of \"BOWLING WORLD\" and think about GUN CONTROL\nlegislation...",
        "\nOh, I get it!!  \"The BEACH goes on\", huh, SONNY??",
        "\nI am a jelly donut.  I am a jelly donut.",
        "\nIs it clean in other dimensions?",
        "\nI'm reporting for duty as a modern person.  I want to do the Latin Hustle now!",
        "\nI hope something GOOD came in the mail today so I have a REASON to live!!",
        "\nI have the power to HALT PRODUCTION on all TEENAGE SEX COMEDIES!!",
        "\nIf I am elected no one will ever have to do their laundry again!",
        "\nIs a tattoo real, like a curb or a battleship?  Or are we suffering in Safeway?",
        "\nCivilization is fun!  Anyway, it keeps me busy!!",
        "\n\t\"These are DARK TIMES for all mankind's HIGHEST VALUES!\"\n\t\"These are DARK TIMES for FREEDOM and PROSPERITY!\"\n\t\"These are GREAT TIMES to put your money on BAD GUY to kick the CRAP\nout of MEGATON MAN!\"",
        "\nSign my PETITION.",
        "\nI once decorated my apartment entirely in ten foot salad forks!!",
        "\nWe have DIFFERENT amounts of HAIR --",
        "\nYow!  Those people look exactly like Donnie and Marie Osmond!!",
        "\nI don't understand the HUMOUR of the THREE STOOGES!!",
        "\nThis PIZZA symbolizes my COMPLETE EMOTIONAL RECOVERY!!",
        "\nHow's the wife?  Is she at home enjoying capitalism?",
        "\n... bleakness ... desolation ... plastic forks ...",
        "\nBo Derek ruined my life!",
        "\nYOW!!  The land of the rising SONY!!",
        "\nThe FALAFEL SANDWICH lands on my HEAD and I become a VEGETARIAN ...",
        "\nUh-oh -- WHY am I suddenly thinking of a VENERABLE religious leader\nfrolicking on a FORT LAUDERDALE weekend?",
        "\nI have accepted Provolone into my life!",
        "\nHUGH BEAUMONT died in 1982!!",
        "\nWhy is it that when you DIE, you can't take your HOME ENTERTAINMENT\nCENTER with you??",
        "\n... I want to perform cranial activities with Tuesday Weld!!",
        "\nIf our behavior is strict, we do not need fun!",
        "\nI'm having a RELIGIOUS EXPERIENCE ... and I don't take any DRUGS",
        "\nIs it NOUVELLE CUISINE when 3 olives are struggling with a scallop in a\nplate of SAUCE MORNAY?",
        "\nI am covered with pure vegetable oil and I am writing a best seller!",
        "\nI've got a COUSIN who works in the GARMENT DISTRICT ...",
        "\nAll right, you degenerates!  I want this place evacuated in 20 seconds!",
        "\nYOW!!!  I am having fun!!!",
        "\nWhile my BRAINPAN is being refused service in BURGER KING, Jesuit\npriests are DATING CAREER DIPLOMATS!!",
        "\nIf I felt any more SOPHISTICATED I would DIE of EMBARRASSMENT!",
        "\nYow!  Now I get to think about all the BAD THINGS I did to a BOWLING\nBALL when I was in JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL!",
        "\nI feel like a wet parking meter on Darvon!",
        "\nYow!  It's some people inside the wall!  This is better than mopping!",
        "\nOnce upon a time, four AMPHIBIOUS HOG CALLERS attacked a family of\nDEFENSELESS, SENSITIVE COIN COLLECTORS and brought DOWN their PROPERTY\nVALUES!!",
        "\nFinally, Zippy drives his 1958 RAMBLER METROPOLITAN into the faculty\ndining room.",
        "\nDisco oil bussing will create a throbbing naugahide pipeline running\nstraight to the tropics from the rug producing regions and devalue the dollar!",
        "\nI'm having a tax-deductible experience!  I need an energy crunch!!",
        "\nCould I have a drug overdose?",
        "\nAwright, which one of you hid my PENIS ENVY?",
        "\nI like your SNOOPY POSTER!!",
        "\nI'm not available for comment..",
        "\nPIZZA!!",
        "\nBELA LUGOSI is my co-pilot ...",
        "\nEverywhere I look I see NEGATIVITY and ASPHALT ...",
        "\nI just forgot my whole philosophy of life!!!",
        "\nI'd like some JUNK FOOD ... and then I want to be ALONE --",
        "\nWhat UNIVERSE is this, please??",
        "\nUh-oh!!  I forgot to submit to COMPULSORY URINALYSIS!",
        "\nOf course, you UNDERSTAND about the PLAIDS in the SPIN CYCLE --",
        "\nXerox your lunch and file it under \"sex offenders\"!",
        "\nCan I have an IMPULSE ITEM instead?",
        "\nTAPPING?  You POLITICIANS!  Don't you realize that the END of the \"Wash\nCycle\" is a TREASURED MOMENT for most people?!",
        "\nCONGRATULATIONS!  Now should I make thinly veiled comments about\nDIGNITY, self-esteem and finding TRUE FUN in your RIGHT VENTRICLE??",
        "\n... I want a COLOR T.V. and a VIBRATING BED!!!",
        "\nI think I am an overnight sensation right now!!",
        "\nI'm meditating on the FORMALDEHYDE and the ASBESTOS leaking into my\nPERSONAL SPACE!!",
        "\nDid I say I was a sardine?  Or a bus???",
        "\nI'm using my X-RAY VISION to obtain a rare glimpse of the INNER\nWORKINGS of this POTATO!!",
        "\nI just had a NOSE JOB!!",
        "\nKids, don't gross me off ... \"Adventures with MENTAL HYGIENE\" can be\ncarried too FAR!",
        "\nif it GLISTENS, gobble it!!",
        "\nLoni Anderson's hair should be LEGALIZED!!",
        "\nI'm wearing PAMPERS!!",
        "\nI left my WALLET in the BATHROOM!!",
        "\nIt's OBVIOUS ... The FURS never reached ISTANBUL ... You were an EXTRA\nin the REMAKE of \"TOPKAPI\" ... Go home to your WIFE ... She's making\nFRENCH TOAST!",
        "\nHere I am in 53 B.C. and all I want is a dill pickle!!",
        "\nCHUBBY CHECKER just had a CHICKEN SANDWICH in downtown DULUTH!",
        "\nOh my GOD -- the SUN just fell into YANKEE STADIUM!!",
        "\nI'm ANN LANDERS!!  I can SHOPLIFT!!",
        "\n... My pants just went on a wild rampage through a Long Island Bowling Alley!!",
        "\nThere's enough money here to buy 5000 cans of Noodle-Roni!",
        "\nPARDON me, am I speaking ENGLISH?",
        "\nDon't worry, nobody really LISTENS to lectures in MOSCOW, either! ...\nFRENCH, HISTORY, ADVANCED CALCULUS, COMPUTER PROGRAMMING, BLACK\nSTUDIES, SOCIOBIOLOGY! ...  Are there any QUESTIONS??",
        "\nHello, GORRY-O!!  I'm a GENIUS from HARVARD!!",
        "\nWhat GOOD is a CARDBOARD suitcase ANYWAY?",
        "\nWhat a COINCIDENCE!  I'm an authorized \"SNOOTS OF THE STARS\" dealer!!",
        "\nZippy's brain cells are straining to bridge synapses ...",
        "\nI'm having fun HITCHHIKING to CINCINNATI or FAR ROCKAWAY!!",
        "\nI am a traffic light, and Alan Ginzberg kidnapped my laundry in 1927!",
        "\nPardon me, but do you know what it means to be TRULY ONE with your BOOTH!",
        "\nI've read SEVEN MILLION books!!",
        "\nThe PILLSBURY DOUGHBOY is CRYING for an END to BURT REYNOLDS movies!!",
        "\nWe place two copies of PEOPLE magazine in a DARK, HUMID mobile home.\n45 minutes later CYNDI LAUPER emerges wearing a BIRD CAGE on her head!",
        "\nA dwarf is passing out somewhere in Detroit!",
        "\nFour thousand different MAGNATES, MOGULS & NABOBS are romping in my\ngothic solarium!!",
        "\nFOOLED you!  Absorb EGO SHATTERING impulse rays, polyester poltroon!!",
        "\nI'm into SOFTWARE!",
        "\nOn the other hand, life can be an endless parade of TRANSSEXUAL\nQUILTING BEES aboard a cruise ship to DISNEYWORLD if only we let it!!",
        "\nShould I do my BOBBIE VINTON medley?",
        "\nOnce, there was NO fun ... This was before MENU planning, FASHION\nstatements or NAUTILUS equipment ... Then, in 1985 ... FUN was\ncompletely encoded in this tiny MICROCHIP ... It contain 14,768 vaguely\namusing SIT-COM pilots!!  We had to wait FOUR BILLION years but we\nfinally got JERRY LEWIS, MTV and a large selection of creme-filled\nsnack cakes!",
        "\nAn Italian is COMBING his hair in suburban DES MOINES!",
        "\nI wonder if I ought to tell them about my PREVIOUS LIFE as a COMPLETE\nSTRANGER?",
        "\nI have many CHARTS and DIAGRAMS..",
        "\nI'm EMOTIONAL now because I have MERCHANDISING CLOUT!!",
        "\nI want a VEGETARIAN BURRITO to go ... with EXTRA MSG!!",
        "\nWhat I want to find out is -- do parrots know much about Astro-Turf?",
        "\nYOW!!  What should the entire human race DO??  Consume a fifth of\nCHIVAS REGAL, ski NUDE down MT. EVEREST, and have a wild SEX WEEKEND!",
        "\nShould I start with the time I SWITCHED personalities with a BEATNIK\nhair stylist or my failure to refer five TEENAGERS to a good OCULIST?",
        "\nOur father who art in heaven ... I sincerely pray that SOMEBODY at this\ntable will PAY for my SHREDDED WHAT and ENGLISH MUFFIN ... and also\nleave a GENEROUS TIP ....",
        "\nMaybe we could paint GOLDIE HAWN a rich PRUSSIAN BLUE --",
        "\nfor ARTIFICIAL FLAVORING!!",
        "\nRHAPSODY in Glue!",
        "\nI smell like a wet reducing clinic on Columbus Day!",
        "\nYow!  I want to mail a bronzed artichoke to Nicaragua!",
        "\nWill the third world war keep \"Bosom Buddies\" off the air?",
        "\nMy CODE of ETHICS is vacationing at famed SCHROON LAKE in upstate New York!!",
        "\nIs he the MAGIC INCA carrying a FROG on his shoulders??  Is the FROG\nhis GUIDELIGHT??  It is curious that a DOG runs already on the ESCALATOR ...",
        "\nSo this is what it feels like to be potato salad",
        "\nWere these parsnips CORRECTLY MARINATED in TACO SAUCE?",
        "\nVICARIOUSLY experience some reason to LIVE!!",
        "\nI hope you millionaires are having fun!  I just invested half your life\nsavings in yeast!!",
        "\nUsed staples are good with SOY SAUCE!",
        "\nI'm also pre-POURED pre-MEDITATED and pre-RAPHAELITE!!",
        "\nBeing a BALD HERO is almost as FESTIVE as a TATTOOED KNOCKWURST.",
        "\nBARRY ... That was the most HEART-WARMING rendition of \"I DID IT MY\nWAY\" I've ever heard!!",
        "\nWhere's th' DAFFY DUCK EXHIBIT??",
        "\nMy life is a patio of fun!",
        "\nYow!",
        "\nCan you MAIL a BEAN CAKE?",
        "\nAm I elected yet?",
        "\nFUN is never having to say you're SUSHI!!",
        "\nIt's the RINSE CYCLE!!  They've ALL IGNORED the RINSE CYCLE!!",
        "\nYow!  I want my nose in lights!",
        "\nIn 1962, you could buy a pair of SHARKSKIN SLACKS, with a \"Continental\nBelt,\" for $10.99!!",
        "\nYow!  Is this sexual intercourse yet??  Is it, huh, is it??",
        "\nInside, I'm already SOBBING!",
        "\nEdwin Meese made me wear CORDOVANS!!",
        "\nI'm ZIPPY the PINHEAD and I'm totally committed to the festive mode.",
        "\nThose aren't WINOS -- that's my JUGGLER, my AERIALIST, my SWORD\nSWALLOWER, and my LATEX NOVELTY SUPPLIER!!",
        "\nMmmmmm-MMMMMM!!  A plate of STEAMING PIECES of a PIG mixed with the\nshreds of SEVERAL CHICKENS!! ... Oh BOY!!  I'm about to swallow a\nTORN-OFF section of a COW'S LEFT LEG soaked in COTTONSEED OIL and\nSUGAR!! ... Let's see ... Next, I'll have the GROUND-UP flesh of CUTE,\nBABY LAMBS fried in the MELTED, FATTY TISSUES from a warm-blooded\nanimal someone once PETTED!! ... YUM!!  That was GOOD!!  For DESSERT,\nI'll have a TOFU BURGER with BEAN SPROUTS on a stone-ground, WHOLE\nWHEAT BUN!!"
      ];
      $("#fortune").text = "\n\n\n\n" + wisdom[Math.floor(Math.random()*wisdom.length)].trim();
    }
	</script>

	<ClientUIDialogPanel class="InWorldInfoPanel AlwaysVisible">
		<Panel class="Page" id="byteframe3">
      <Label id="count" class="Desc" text="undefined" />
      <Panel class="TextArea Big">
        <Label id="fortune" class="Text" style="font-size: 42px; color: blue;" text="undefined" />
      </Panel>
      <Panel class="ButtonControls">
        <Panel class="InfoDialogButton">
          <Button id="ResetFallout" class="DialogButton Visible" onactivate="ResetFallout()">
            <Label text="Reset Fallout" />
          </Button>
        </Panel>
      </Panel>
      <Panel class="InfoDialogButton" style="width: 100%;">
        <Button id="ChangeFortune" class="DialogButton Visible" onactivate="ChangeFortune()">
          <Label text="New Fortune" />
        </Button> 
      </Panel>
		</Panel>
	</ClientUIDialogPanel>

</root>